{"quiz1" :[
  {
    "id" : 1,
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Python is an Interpreted Language",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
 {  
   "id" : 2,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What is the result of the following code: System.out.println(10 % 3);",
    "correctAnswer" : "1",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
  },
  {  
    "id" : 3,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What transmits between two networks?",
    "correctAnswer" : "router",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
  },
  {"id" : 4,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "OS stands for operating system",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {"id" : 5,   
   "questionType" : "multiple",
    "questionText" : "A Compiled Language is",
    "correctAnswer" : "A language that is completely converted into executable format",
    "options" : ["A language that is completely converted into executable format", "A lanuguage excecuted line by line","A lanugage put together","does not exist"]
  },
  {"id" : 6,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "A GUI stands for a graphical user interface",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  }, {"id" : 7,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What is an ERD?",
    "correctAnswer" : "Entity Relationship Diagram",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"},
  {"id" : 8,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What is a RAD?",
    "correctAnswer" : "Rapid Application Development",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"},
  {"id" : 9,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "How do you comment out only a single line in JavaScript?",
    "correctAnswer" : "//",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"},
  {"id" : 10   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "How do you comment out an entire chunk of code?",
    "correctAnswer" : "/**/",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"},
    {"id" : 11,   
   "questionType" : "multiple",
    "questionText" : "CSS is",
    "correctAnswer" : "Cascading Style Sheets",
    "options" : ["Corresponding Sheets Styling", "Cascading Style Sheets","Cascading Sheets of Style","Correspoding Style Sheets"]
  },
  {"id" : 12,   
   "questionType" : "multiple",
    "questionText" : "In JS, declaring a variable is",
    "correctAnswer" : "var i",
    "options" : ["var i", "int i;","var i: 0;","i"]
  },
  {"id" : 13,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "There are only 6 headings in HTML",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {"id" : 14,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "<p> is the tag for a paragraph in HTML",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  

  
]
  
}
